David C. Mahoney Company Records
Hartford History Center, Hartford Public Library
- Items
  - 63-65 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 3. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing house and garage, and one photograph of the house. (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - 66 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 11. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing two houses, and one photograph of one of the houses. (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - 67 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #3, Parcel 2. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing house and garage, and one photograph of the house. (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - 68 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 10. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing two houses, and one photograph of one of the houses. (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - 82 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 7. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan, and one photograph of a house. (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - 84 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 6. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan showing building and garage, and one photograph of the brick three-family dwelling. (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - 86 Laurel Street, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 5. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan, and one photograph of the house. (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Laurel Street, west side, 1962; Block #2, Parcel 4. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan, and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - 330-340 Main Street, 1961; Block #6, Parcel 7. Typescript description, site plan and one photograph of a brick store and apartment building housing Lundberg's Dry Cleaners. (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - 350 Main Street, 1962; Block #6, Parcel 6. Typescript description, site plan and two photographs of a parking lot and brick building. (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - 356-360 Main Street, 1962?; Block #6, Parcel 5. Typescript description, site plan and three photographs of a parking lot and a store and theater building housing the Crown Theater and Galinski Travel Agency. (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - 368-376 Main Street/65-69 South Prospect Street, 1962?; Block #6, Parcel 4. Typescript description, site plan, and two photographs showing a building housing apartments, the Crown Theater, and stores, including Capitol Motors, an automobile dealership with signs that read "Chevrolet Sales and Service." (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - 406-410 Main Street/37-41 South Prospect Street, 1962?; Block #6, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan showing two buildings, and two photographs of a brick store and rooming house and a warehouse with a sign that reads "Waller and Osborn." (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - 571-575 Main Street, 1962?; Block #2, Parcel 8. Site plan, and one photograph of a commercial building housing the Silver Tap Grill. (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - 583 Main Street, 1962?; Block #2, Parcel 6. Site plan and one photograph showing both 571-581 Main Street, housing the Silver Tap Grill, and 583 Main Street, a small two-story commercial building. Loew's Poli Theater is visible at the right. (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - 589-593 Main Street, 1962?; Block #2, Parcel 5. Brief typescript description, site plan, and one photograph of the Loew's Poli Theater. (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - 599-613 Main Street/21-45 Mulberry Street/126 Wells Street, 1962?; Block #1, Parcel 1. Four site plans and two photographs of Main Street frontage and Mulberry Street building. (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - 629-653 Main Street, 1962?; Block #1, Parcel #1. 10 plans and one photograph of a commercial block including the Loew's Poli Palace Theater, Vogel Jewelers, and an artist's supply store. (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - 746-760 Main Street, 1965; Typescript and one photograph of the Hartford-Connecticut Trust building including buses parked in front of the Old State House and a crane at a construction site on the opposite side of Main Street. (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - 777 Main Street/80 Farmington Avenue, 1962; Brief typescript with one photograph of a modern office building located at 80 Farmington Avenue; Fee owner, Hartford National Bank and Trust was located at 777 Main Street. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 973-931 Main Street, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 10. Typescript, site plan, and one photograph of a building housing Sam's Army Navy Store, Allen's Package Store, Planters Peanuts, and Wynshaws Bridal Shoppe. Kay Jewelers is next door. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - 983-989 Main Street, 1969; Block #1, Parcel 9. Typescript, site plan, and five photographs of an office building and stores including Sherrow's Textiles, the Ham-Egger Coffee Shop, and other businesses. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - 995-1001 Main Street, 1969?; Block #1, Parcel 8. Typescript, site plan, and three photographs showing Sherrow's Textiles, the Ham-Egger Coffee Shop, Kaufman Luggage, and La Strada Restaurant. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - 1003-1027 Main Street, 1969?; Block #1, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan and three photographs showing Sherrow's Textiles, the Ham-Egger Coffee Shop, Art Clothes Chop, the Strand Theater, Balley's Shoes, and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - 1026-1028 Main Street, 1963; Brochure for a seven-story office building located near Sherrow's Textiles, Youth Centre, and G. Fox & Co. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - 1029-1031 Main Street, 1964; Brochure for a seven-story office building located near Sherrow's Textiles, Youth Centre, and G. Fox & Co. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - 1123-1129 Main Street/412-416 Trumbull, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 2. Typescript, site plan, and one photograph showing a store, office, and tenement building housing Embers Restaurant, Jules Shop for Men, Griswold Drug, and Williams Herbert Co. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - 1143-1159 Main Street/405-410 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #2, Parcel 1. Typescript, site plan and three photographs and negatives showing brick tenement and tore building housing Fashion Shoe Store, State Loan Company, Patti Restaurant, Patsy's Package Store, and Capitol Office Furniture. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - 1638-1642 Main Street, 196-?; Typescript and three photographs of an apartment building and stores including Rodriguez Candy Store, a package store, and the Plaza Hotel. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Main Street, northwest corner/Wells Street, 1963; Typescript and one photograph of the property in back of Loew's Poli Theater. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Main Street, southwest corner/Mulberry Street, 1965; Typescript and one photograph of brick store and tenement building, an intersection, and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Main Street west/Church Street, east side, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 3B. Site plan and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Main Street, west/Trumbull Street, south, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 1. Site plan and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Main Street, west, See Elm Street, south side. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - 41-53 Mechanic Street, 1967; Brief typescript with one photograph of a parking lot and an old tobacco warehouse. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Miscellaneous pictures of Hartford, 1958-1965; Photographs include buildings on Charter Oak Place, Columbia Street, Farmington Avenue, Goodman Place, Orchard Street, Pleasant Street, Portland Street, Union Place, Village Street, and Windsor Street and aerial views of Hartford. Some photographs are unidentified. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Mulberry Street, See Main Street, southwest corner. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - 21-45 Mulberry Street, See 599-613 Main Street. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - 53 Mulberry Street, 196-?; Site plan and one photograph of buildings housing Tommy's Trading Post and Burt and Dell. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - 65-81 Mulberry Street/144-146 Wells Street, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 4. Site plan of property at the corner of Wells Street and Mulberry Street. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - 145 Pearl Street, 1964; Block #8, Parcel 1. Typescript, site plan, and one photograph of a Cities Service gasoline service station, a parking lot, and a crane on a corner lot. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - 1 State House Square, 1983; Photographs taken just before demolition for 1 State House Square include American Discount Stores, Ann Joe's Card and Bookstore, Archer Kent Discount Health & Beauty Aids, Blutstein Wholesale Retail, Fabian's Grinders & Pizza, G. C. Lawson Farms Ice Cream, Hartford Stage Company, Hartford Wigs, Harvey & Lewis Opticians (with details of the gargoyles), Herb's Sport Shop, J. Van der Voorn Bake Shop, Mary Jane, Morse Shoes, National Discount Stores, Northeast Savings, Razon's Discount Center, a United States Post Office, Wilfred Academy Beauty School, and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - 1 State House Square, See Sheldon Street, north side. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - 23 Prospect Street, 1967; Brief typescript and two photographs the former Knights of Columbus club building. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - 7-23 Riverside Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 4. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - 27 Riverside Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 3. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of two multiple-family dwellings and an iron fence. (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - 33 Riverside Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 2. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and two photographs of a two-family frame house. (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - 35-43 Riverside Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 1. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and two photographs of the front and back of two three-family dwellings and a bar and grill. (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Sheldon-Charter Oak Section A Redevelopment Area, 1965; Typescript and nineteen photographs of houses, apartment buildings and stores at 183-185 Babcock Street, 126-128 Babcock Street, 54-56 Cedar Street, 7 Columbia Street, 63 Franklin Avenue, 81-83 Franklin Avenue, 125-127 Franklin Avenue, 223-225 Franklin Avenue, 393 Franklin Avenue, 440-442 Franklin Avenue, 16-18 Governor Street, 144-146 Governor Street, 59 Grand Street, 248-250 Hudson Street, 529-533 Hudson Street, 413-427 Hudson Street, 47-49 Huyshope Avenue, 206 Jefferson Street, 307-313 Wethersfield Avenue. (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Sheldon Street, 1965?; Three photographs and negatives of 77-83 Sheldon Street, 93-95 Sheldon Street, and 99-103 Sheldon Street, housing the Times Package Store, the Sheldon Restaurant, and John Chung Laundry and Dry Cleaning. (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - 79-103 Sheldon Street/8-24 South Prospect Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 14. Typescript description, site plan and four photographs of six brick tenement and store buildings housing a laundromat, Charter Oak Lunch, C & L Market, and the Cricket Restaurant, and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - 111-113 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 13. Typescript description, site plan and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - 116-134 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 10. Site plan of property with two two-story buildings. (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - 135 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 12. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of a brick building housing Libby & Blinn, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - 143-149 Sheldon Street/133-139 Governor Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 11. Typescript description, site plan and eight photographs of two tenement and store buildings, a garage and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - 151 Sheldon Street, See 159-161 Governor Street. (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - 154-156 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 9. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of a building housing Eddie's Restaurant and Dance Hall. (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - 170-180 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 7. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of a brick building housing the Governor Restaurant and a barber shop. (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - 184-186 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 6. Typescript, site plan, and one photograph of a brick store building housing a barber shop and other businesses. (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - 189-195 Sheldon Street/158-160 Governor Street, 1965?; Block #4, Parcel 4. Typescript description, site plan and two negatives and photographs of two brick tenement and store buildings housing the Union Baking Company, Inc., and a lunch room and pool room. (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - 192-194 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 5. Brief typescript assessment, site plan, and one photograph of a brick tenement and store building. (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - 197-201 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #4, Parcels 2 and 3. Brief typescript assessments, site plans, and one photograph and negative each of two commercial buildings housing Farber's and the State Vending Co. (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - 200-203 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 4. Site plan showing two buildings. (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - 212 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 3. Brief typescript, site plan and three photographs of tenement and store buildings housing La Pizza and Sal's Package Store. (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - 216-218 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 2. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of a building housing Sal's Package Store. (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - 217-225 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #4, Parcel 1. Site plan and two negatives and photographs of the Mingo Tavern and a two-car garage. (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - 235-273 Sheldon Street, 1965?; Block #3, Parcel 1. Site plan and three negatives and photographs of a large parking lot and two small buildings, one of them housing a restaurant. (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - 237 Sheldon Street/26 Union Street, 1965?; Block #2, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan, and three negatives and photographs of an office, shop, and storage building housing C. H. Dresser & Son, Inc. (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - 307-337 Sheldon Street, See 96-104 Charter Oak Avenue. (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Sheldon Street, north side, 1965?; Block #1, Parcels 8 and 11. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and photograph of each of two properties, one a vacant lot beside Baronet Coffee, the other a gangway between two commercial buildings. (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Sheldon Street, north/Columbus Boulevard, west side, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 1. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of vacant land at the corner of Sheldon Street and Columbus Boulevard. (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - Sheldon Street, north/Prospect Street, east, 1965?; Block #1, Parcel 12. Brief typescript, site plan, negative and one photograph of a vacant lot with grass and shrubs. (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - 8-24 South Prospect Street, See 79-103 Sheldon Street. (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - 30-32 South Prospect Street, 196-?; Brief typescript description, site plan, negative and photograph of an office, factory and warehouse building formerly belonging to the Allen Manufacturing Co. (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - 37-41 South Prospect Street, See 406-410 Main Street. (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - 42-44 South Prospect Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 16. Typescript description, site plan, and three negatives and photographs of a brick store and apartment building and a club and tenement building. (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - 48-50 South Prospect Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 17. Typescript description, site plan, and two negatives and photographs of two three-family dwellings and a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - 56-58 South Prospect Street, 1965; Block #5, Parcel 18. Typescript description, site plan, and two negatives and four photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - 62 South Prospect Street, 1965; Block #5, Parcel 20. Typescript description, site plan, and two negatives and four photographs of a parking lot. Typescript description, site plan, and three photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - 65-69 South Prospect Street, See 368-376 Main Street. (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - 68 South Prospect Street, 1965; Block #5, Parcel 21. Typescript description, site plan, and two photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - 70-72 South Prospect Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 22. Typescript description, site plan, negatives and one photograph of a parking lot and an office and tenement building. (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - 80 South Prospect Street, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 23. Typescript description, site plan, negative and one photograph of a garage and warehouse building housing the Battery & Ignition Co. (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - South Prospect Street, east side, 1965?; Block #5, Parcel 19. Typescript description, site plan, and three photographs of a parking lot. (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - 24 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #6, Parcel 1. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - 6-8 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #6, Parcel 2. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - 9-11 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 6. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - 10-12 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #6, Parcel 3. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - 13-15 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 7. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - 15-16 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #6, Parcel 4. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling (hidden by trees). (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - 17-19 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 8. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a brick, six-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - 21 South Woodbine Street, 1962; Block #5, Parcel 9. Typescript real estate appraisal, site plan and one photograph of a frame, three-family dwelling. (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Trumbull Street Redevelopment Project, 1962; Brief typescripts and eighteen photographs of property at 206-236 Asylum Street, northeast corner of Pearl and Trumbull Streets, 219 Church Street, 48-54 1/2 Allyn Street, southwest corner of Pearl and Trumbull Streets, 151 Church Street, 62-72 Church Street, 250-256 Asylum Street, 160-164 Ann Street, 405-409 Trumbull Street, 1029-1031 Main Street, 75 Pearl Street, 49 Pearl Street and 62-72 Church Street, including many parking lots and businesses. (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Trumbull Street, See Asylum Street, northwest corner. (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - 85 Trumbull Street, 1966; Parcel #2, Block 8. Typescript description, site plan, and eight photographs of a brick industrial building, formerly the property of Connecticut Printers, and a parking lot. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - 94 Trumbull Street, 196-?; Block #9, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan, and three negatives and photographs of an office and warehouse building and a parking lot. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - 247-273 Trumbull Street, See 10-16 Allyn Street (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - 262-264 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #4, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick commercial building housing Reichlin Furriers. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - 270-290 Trumbull Street/97-103 Church Street, 1964; Block #4, Parcel 1. Typescript description, site plan, and two negative and photographs of two store and tenement buildings housing Eagle Shoe Service, Lloyd's Furrier, the Music Centre and other businesses. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - 285-289 Trumbull Street, See 135-141 Church Street. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - 301-315 Trumbull Street/97-103 Church Street, 1964; Block #3, Parcel 3. Typescript description, site plan, and three negatives and photographs of a store and hotel building housing Spear & McManus Florists and the Hotel Claret. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - 306-318 Trumbull Street/96-112 Church Street, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 18. Typescript description, site plan, and three negatives and photographs showing brick store and tenement buildings housing a barber shop, Central Lunch, and other businesses. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - 321-333 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #3, Parcel 1. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a store, office and lodge hall building housing the Schneider Art Studio, the Electronic Jungle, and a dance studio. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - 330-338 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #1, Parcel 5. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick building used as the headquarters for the Salvation Army and a men's hotel. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - 335 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #3, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick warehouse building. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - 339-403 Trumbull Street, 1964; Block #2, Parcel 2. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a store, garage and storage building housing a Goodyear Tire Center and an electronics recording studio. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - 405-419 Trumbull Street, See 1143-1159 North Main Street. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - 412-416 Trumbull Street, See 1123-1129 Main Street. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Trumbull Street, east side, 1964?; Block #9, Parcel 1A. Site plan, and one negative and photograph of a gangway between two brick buildings. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Trumbull Street, south side, See Main Street, west side. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Trumbull Street, southwest corner/Allyn Street, 1966; Block #6, Parcel 1. Typescript description, two site plans, and one negative and three photographs of a parking lot and parking garage. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Trumbull Street, west side, 1964; Block 8, Parcel 2A. Typescript description and brochure containing Building Information concerning a printing plant that belonged to Connecticut Printers and Case, Lockwood & Brainard Co. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - 1 Union Street, See 96-104 Charter Oak Avenue. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - 2-4 and 10-12 Union Street, See 96-104 Charter Oak Avenue. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - 6-8 Union Street, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 5. Typescript description, site plan, and one photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - 14-16 Union Street, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 4. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - 14-16 Union Street, 1961; Block #3, Parcel 8. Typescript description, site plan, three floor plans and three negatives and photographs of five interconnected brick workshop, storage, and office buildings. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - 18-20 Union Street, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 3. Typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - 26 Union Street, See 287 Sheldon Street. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - 27 Union Street, 1964?; Block #3, Parcel 7. Brief typescript description, site plan, and one negative and photograph of a brick six-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 70 Wells Street, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 10. Brief typescript description, site plan, and photograph of Cities Service Station and the back of Loew's Theater. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - 126 Wells Street, See 599-613 Main Street. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - 144-146 Wells Street, See 65-81 Mulberry Street. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - 162-180 Wells Street, 1964?; Block #1, Parcel 3. Site plan and two photographs of the Heublein Hotel, Heublein Coffee Shop, and Heublein Men's Bar. (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - 70 Wells Street, west, 1964?; Block #2, Parcel 9. Typescript description, site plan, and one photograph of the property, a vacant lot behind Loew's Theater used as a parking lot. (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - 65 Wethersfield Avenue, 1973; Typescript description and one three photographs of a former dwelling partially converted to an office building. (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - 11 Willow Street, 1962; Typescript real estate appraisal with one photograph of a frame two-family house converted into a one-family dwelling. (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - 12-14 Willow Street, See 33-35 Laurel Street. (Box 4, Folder 34)